(Penny:)What did we say about
being a nicer friend?
(Leonard:)-Thank you.
-Leonard, what did we say
(Penny:)about being a gullible weenie?
(Sheldon:)-It is just so frustrating.
-'Causee you're trying too hard.
(Penny:)You need to do something else.
Get your mind off it.
(Leonard:)Hey, how about we bring back
Anything Can Happen Thursdays?
(Penny:)Hey, that's good.
Why'd you guys stop doing that?
(Leonard:)You made fun of us.
Said it was stupid.
(Penny:)Yeah. Sounds like me.
(Penny:)Come on, Sheldon.
What do you say'?
(Sheldon:)All right. I officially reinstate
Anything Can Happen Thursday.
Great!
What do you want to do?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)I'm starting to remember the problem
with Anything Can Happen Thursdays.
I (THEME SONG PLAYING) I